Guide to the Andrew F. Smith Collection of Cookery Ephemera MSS.295
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Cookery Ephemera, 1798-2009
  - Pacific Coast Borax Company, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    Pacific Coast Borax Co. First Aid for Housekeeping. New York, NY: Pacific Coast Borax Co., 1934.
  - Pain, Alfonso C., 1981 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Paine, Diehl & Company, circa 1850s (Box 29, Folder 21)
    Paine, Diehl & Co. The P. D. and Co. Keystone Cook Book. Philadelphia, PA: Paine, Diehl & Co., undated.
  - The Palisade Manufacturing Company, 1921 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    Palisade. Andrea, A. Louise. The Secret of his Mother's Cooking... Kitchen Bouquet. New York, NY: Palisade Manufacturing Co. 1921.
  - Pan-American Coffee Bureau, National Coffee Council, circa 1940 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Panni, The Time Saver, circa 1930-1940s (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Park & Tilford, 1906 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    Park & Tilford. Catalogue of Fine Groceries. New York, NY: Park & Tilford, Summer & Spring 1906.
  - Parker, Marian Jane, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Selected Recipes and Menus for Parties, Holidays, and Special Occasions
  - Park Avenue Imports, circa 1970s (Box 29, Folder 26)
    Park Avenue Imports. The Story of Sabra Imported Liqueur. New York, NY: Park Avenue Imports, undated.
  - Pasadena Women's Committee, circa 1918 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - The Pastry Book, circa 1900 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Paul F. Skinner Manufacturing Company, circa 1920s (Box 29, Folder 29)
    Skinner Manufacturing Co. Skinner's Macaroni Cook Book. Second Edition. Omaha: Skinner Manufacturing Co., undated.
  - Peanut Research, circa 1920-1990s (Box 30, Folder 1-2, Box 29, Folder 30)
    Tice & Co. "Verhampshire Pure Peanut Butter." Boston, MA: C. M. Tice & Co., undated.
    Georgia Peanut Commission. Owens, Betsy, and Marilyn Hubert. Peanuts and Pizzazz to Meals & Snacks. Tifton, GA: Georgia Peanut Commission, undated.
    Huntley Manufacturing Co. Monitor Peanut Cleaning, Shelling, Grading and Roasting Machinery. Catalog No. 69. Silver Creek, NY: Huntley Manufacturing Co., undated.
  - Peck, Stow & Wilcox Company, 1898 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Peck, Stow & Wilcox Co. McMurphy, Harriet S. The Ideal Receipt Book. Southington, CT & New York: The Peck, Stow & Wilcox Co., 1898.
  - Peerless Cooker Company, circa 1850s (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Peerless Cooker Co. Directions for Using the Peerless Steam Cooker. Buffalo, NY: Peerless Cooker Co., undated.
  - Penick & Ford, Ltd., circa 1900-1920s (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Penick & Ford. The Sweetest Story Ever Told; A Story of the Southland. New Orleans, LA: Penick & Ford, Ltd., undated.
    Penick & Ford, Ltd. Brer Rabbit's Modern Recipes for the Modern Hostess. New Orleans, LA: Penick & Ford, Ltd., undated.
  - The Peninsular Stove Company, circa 1900-1920s (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Pennsylvania Grocer, 1888 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania Salt Manufacturing Company; Perfection Products, 1876, circa 1920s (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Pennsylvania Salt Manufacturing Co. Bi-Carbonate of Soda. Philadelphia, PA: Pennsylvania Salt Manufacturing Co., 1876.
  - Perky, H. D., 1898 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Natural Food Co. Perky, H. D. The Vital Question and Our Navy 1898. Worcester, MA: H. D. Perky, 1897.
  - Peter Eckrich & Sons, Inc., 1941, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Eckrich & Sons, Inc. The Eckrich Book of Picnics. Place of publication unknown: Peter Eckrich & Sons, Inc., 1941.
    Eckrich & Sons, Inc. 14 Favorite Meals with Smoked Sausage. Fort Wayne: Peter Eckrich & Sons, Inc., undated.
    Eckrich & Sons, Inc. Keep this under Your Hat. Recipes for Special Occasions from Eckrich. Fort Wayne: Peter Eckrich & Sons, Inc., 1974.
  - Peter Robinson's, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Pet Milk Company; Musselman's, 1934-1960s (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Pet Milk Company. New Summertime Recipes for the New Pet Milk. St. Louis, MO: Pet Milk Company, 1934.
    Pet Milk Company. Taylor, Mary Lee. Satisfying Food for Any Family. St. Louis, MO: Pet Milk Company, undated.
    Pet Milk Company. Mary Lee Taylor's Mealtime Magic for 2 or 4 or 6. St. Louis, MO: Pet Milk Company, undated.
    Pet Milk. Taylor, Mary Lee. One-Dish Meals, Salads and Desserts. St. Louis, MO: Pet Milk Company, undated.
  - Pettiford's Bakery--General Foods, circa 1920s (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Pillsbury; Pillsbury Mills, Inc.; Globe Mills, 1914-1988 (Box 30, Folder 12-17)
    Pillsbury Flour Mills Company. 100 Delicious Foods from 4 Basic Recipes. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Flour Mills Co., 1923.
    Pillsbury's. Pillsbury's Best Flour Sure A Receipt Book. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Flour Mills Company, undated.
    Pillsbury Flour Mills Company. 15 Wonderful Recipes Inside– Look. Minneapolis, MN: The Pillsbury Flour Mills Co., circa 1932.
    Pillsbury Flour Mills Company. Your Family's Food. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Flour Mills Company, undated.
    Pillsbury. "Vitos, The Ideal Wheat Food for Breakfast." Minneapolis, MN: The Pillsbury-Washburn Flour Mills Co., Ltd., circa 1920s.
    Globe Mills. Practical Recipes tested for Home Use. Los Angeles, CA: Globe Mills, 1926.
    Pillsbury Flour Mills Company. The Pillsbury Cook Book. A New Edition. Minneapolis, MN: The Pillsbury Flour Mills Co., 1921.
    Pillsbury Mills, Inc. Baking's Fun with Globe "A1". Los Angeles, CA: Ann West Globe Mills, Pillsbury Mills, Inc., 1948.
    Pillsbury Company. Short-Cur Breads. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Company, undated.
    Pillsbury. Pillsbury's Best Butter Cookie Cookbook. Volume 11. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury, undated.
    Pillsbury. Pillsbury's Best 12th Grand National Bake-Off Cookbook. Place of publication unknown: Pillsbury, undated.
    Pillsbury Company. Butter Cookie Booklet; 25 Cookie Recipes. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Company, undated.
    Pillsbury Company. Pillsbury's 24 Meat 'n Potato Ideas Adapted by Ann Pillsbury. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Company, undated.
    Pillsbury. 100 Prize-winning Recipes Adapted for Your Use by Ann Pillsbury. From Pillsbury's 2nd Grand National Recipe & Baking Contest, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NYC, December 11, 1950. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Mills, Inc., 1951.
    Pillsbury. From Pillsbury's 4th Grand National 100,00 Recipe and Baking Contest: 100 Prize-Winning Recipes Adopted for Your Use by Ann Pillsbury. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Mills, Inc., undated.
    Pillsbury Company. Pillsbury's Meat Cook Book. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Company, 1969.
    Pillsbury. More Lovin' from the Oven; Generations of Baking Favorites. Minneapolis, MN: Pillsbury Company, 1988.
  - Pine Tree State Rebekah Cook Book, circa 1850s (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Pinkham, Lydia E., undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Fruits and Candies
  - Planters Edible Oil Company, 1948, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Planters Edible Oil Co. Cooking the Modern Way: 129 Ways to Better Meals. Suffolk, VA, Wilkes-Barre, PA: Planters Edible Oil Co., 1948.
    Planters Edible Oil Co. They Taste So-o-o Good. Suffolk, VA, Wilkes-Barre, PA, Toronto, Canada Suffolk, VA, Wilkes-Barre, PA, Toronto, Canada: Planters Edible Oil Company, 1955.
  - Planters Nut & Chocolate Company, 1920 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Planters. Around the World with Mr. Peanuts. Wilkes-Barre, PA: The Planters Nut & Chocolate Company, 1920.
  - Planters Peanut Oil--Standard Brands, Inc., 1961, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Planters Peanut Oil. Appliance Cooking for All Seasons. Place of publication unknown: Planters Peanut Oil, undated.
    Planters. Beard, James. How to Cook Better with Planters French-Process Peanut Oil. Place of publication unknown: Planters Peanuts, a Division of Standard Brands, Inc., 1961.
    Planters. Mr. Peanut's Guide to Nutrition. New York, NY: Standard Brands, Inc., 1970.
    Planters. Post Card, mentions Planters Website. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - The Pocumtuc Housewife: A Guide to Domestic Cookery, 1925 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Pool Brothers, 1881 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Pool, Nazro, Kimball & Company, 1870 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Portable Electric Mixer, circa 1950s (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Electric Portable Mixer. Delightful Recipes to Prepare with Your Portable Electric Mixer. Place of publication unknown: Electric Portable Mixer, undated.
  - Popcorn Research, 1900-1990s (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Advance Manufacturing Co. "15000 Other Merchants Have Chose Advance Light Lunch and Popcorn Equipment." St. Louis, MO: Advance Manufacturing Co., circa 1936.
    Cretors. "The Cash Rolls in When There's a Cretors in the Door." Chicago, IL: C. Cretors Co., undated.
    Holcomb & Hoke Mtg. Co. Sundry Price List for Butter-Kist Machines. Indianapolis, IN: Holcomb & Hoke Manufacturing Co., 1919.
    Holcomb & Hoke Mtg. Co. Butter-Kist Popcorn. Indianapolis, IN: Holcomb & Hoke Manufacturing Co.
    Kendall & Whitney. "K & W Eureka Popping Corn." Portland, ME: Kendall & Whitney, undated.
  - Postcards of Restaurants, 1920-1940s (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Postum Cereal Company, Inc., 1914-1928 (Box 31, Folder 9-11)
    Postum Cereal Company. The Road to Wellville. Battle Creek, MI: Postum Cereal Co., Ltd., undated.
    Postum Cereal Company. Coffee Drinking and Postum. Battle Creek, MI: Postum Cereal Company, Ltd., undated.
    Postum Cereal Company. Emmons, Minnie Alice, comp. Good Things to Eat from Wellville. Battle Creek, MI: Postum Cereal Company, Ltd., 1915.
    Postum Cereal Company. 101 Prize Recipes Printed from Contest Conducted by Postum Cereal Company, Inc. Battle Creek, MI: Postum Cereal Company, 1924.
    Postum Cereal Company. McGovern, Arthur A. A Book of Better Breakfasts. Battle Creek, MI: Postum Cereal Co., 1925.
    General Foods. The School Lunch. New York, NY: Education Department of General Foods Corporation, 1928.
    Postum Cereal Company. The Wonderful Lunch Boxes. Battle Creek, MI: Educational Department, Postum Cereal Company, Inc., 1925.
  - Poultry & Egg National Board, circa 1940-1950s (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Poultry and Egg National Board, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Let's Have a Barbecue!
  - Poultry Science Association; Premier Malt Products, Inc., 1951, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Presbyterian Church of Lexington, NE, circa 1920-1940s (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Price Compound Company; Price Baking Powder Company; Price Flavoring Extract Company, 1887-1921 (Box 31, Folder 15-18)
    Price Compound Co. Mrs. Price's Complete Directions for Canning Vegetables and Fruits, Pickling, etc. Minneapolis, MN: Price Compound Co., undated.
    Price Baking Powder Co. Table and Kitchen. Chicago, IL: Price Baking Powder Co., 1912.
    Price Flavoring Extract Co. Dr. Price's Delicious Desserts. New York, NY & Chicago, IL: Price Flavoring Extract Co., undated.
    Price Flavoring Extract Co. Dr. Price's Excellent Recipes for Delicious Desserts. New York, NY & Chicago, IL: Price Flavoring Extract Co., undated.
    Price Flavoring Extract Co. Dr. Price's Delicious Desserts. 40th Edition. New York, NY & Chicago, IL: Price Flavoring Extract Co., 1904.
  - Prince Macaroni Company, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Prince Marconi Company. Prince Golden Macaroni Recipes. Boston, MA: Prince Macaroni Company, 1951.
  - Procter & Gamble Company, 1923-1949, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 2-5)
    Procter & Gamble Co. Neil, Marion Harris. A Modern Manual of Cooking. Cincninnati: Procter & Gamble Company, 1923.
    Procter & Gamble Co. Neil, Marion Harris. Mrs. Neil's Cooking Secrets. Cincinnati, OH: Procter & Gamble Company, 1924.
    Procter & Gamble Co. Home Economics Department. French Frying. Cincninnati: Home Economics Department, Procter & Gamble, 1932.
    Procter & Gamble Co. Home Economics Department. School Lunches. Manual No. 10. Place of publication unknown: Procter & Gamble Co., 1926.
    Procter & Gamble Co. Carter, Winifred S. Good Things to Eat from Out of the Air; 136 Tested Radio Recipes. Cincninnati: Procter & Gamble, 1932.
    Procter & Gamble Co. Carter, Winifred S. Cooking Hints and Tested Recipes. Cincinnati, OH: Procter & Gamble Company, 1937.
    Procter and Gamble. Choosey Mothers' Peanut Butter Cookbook. Cincinnati, OH: Procter and Gamble Company, 1979.
  - Proctor & Wood, 1851 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - The Producers' Price Current, 1866-1884 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - The Prudential Insurance Company of America, circa 1900-1920s (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Prudential. The Prudential Cook Book and Household Hints. NY: Gray Lith Co., undated.
  - Pure Food Products--Beech-Nut Brand, 1920 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Beech-Nut Packing Co. A Hundred & One Recipes with Beech-Nut Peanut Butter. Third Edition. Canajoharie, NY: Beech-Nut Packing Co., circa 1920.
  - Pure Food Show, 1899 (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 13)
  - Purssell Manufacturing Company; Pruitt's Pure Sea Kelp, circa 1900-1920s, circa 1950s (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Pruitt's. Food and Our Bodies. Pruitt's Pure Sea Kelp (brochure). Place of publication unknown: Pruitt's, undated.
  - The Quaker Oats Company, circa 1940-1950s (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Quaker Oats Company. Quaker Surprise Recipes 32 New Recipes and Pictures. Chicago, IL: Quaker Oats Company, undated.
    Quaker Oats Company. America's Most Famous Recipe. Place of publication unknown: Quaker Oats Company, undated.
  - Qualitee Dairy Products Company, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Qualitee Dairy Products Company. Helps for Homemakers; A Cook Book of 177 Kitchen Tested Original Recipes. San Diego: Qualitee Dairy Products Company, 1932.
  - Ralston Purina Company, 1926, 1928, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 13, Box 44, Folder 15)
    Ralston Purina Company. Health, Growth and Happiness for Boys and Girls A Mother's Manual. St. Louis, MO: Ralston Purina Company, 1926.
    Ralston Purina Company. Recipes from Checkerboard Square. St. Louis, MO: Ralston Purina Company, undated.
    Ralston Purina Company. A Mother's Manual. St. Louis, MO: Ralston Purina Company, 1928.
  - Ramirez & Feraud Chili Company, Inc., circa 1960s (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Rand Sea Moss Farine Company, circa 1900 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    Rand Sea Moss Farine Co. One Hundred New and Original Recipes. New York, NY: Rand Sea Moss Farine Co., undated.
  - Ransom, Hamlin & Company, 1872 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Ransom, Hamlin & Co. Ransom, Hamlin & Co.'s Family Almanac and Receipt Book. Buffalo: Ransom, Hamlin & Co., 1872.
  - Ranstead, Carey & Company, 1879 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - R. B. Davis Company, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    R. B. Davis. Davis Master Pattern Baking Formulas. Second Edition. Hoboken, NJ: R. B. Davis Company, 1940.
  - R.C. Williams & Company, 1898 (Box Shared Fales 003, Folder 4)
  - Realemon Foods; The Reader's Digest Association; R.C. Bigelow, Inc., circa 1970-1980s (Box 32, Folder 19)
    R. C. Bigelow, Inc. Superb Summer Drinks Start with Bigelow Teas 12 Delicious Recipes. Place of publication unknown: R. C. Bigelow, Inc., undated.
  - Recipes, 1895-2007 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Recipes of New England Housewives, circa 1850s (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Red Rock, circa 1920-1940s (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Reid-Murdoch & Company, 1906 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    Reid-Murdoch & Co. The Record Breaker –Crawford Cheese Announcement. Chicago, IL: Reid-Murdoch & Co., 1906.
  - Reliable Flour Company, 1904-1915 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    Reliable Flour. Reliable Recipes No. 1. Boston, MA: Reliable Flour Company, 1904.
    Reliable Flour. Reliable Recipes Number Two. Boston, MA: Reliable Flour Company, 1907.
    Reliable Flour. Would You Like to Make–Good Cake?. Boston, MA: Reliable Flour Co., undated.
    Reliable Flour. Biscuit and Cakes; The "Reliable" Method. Boston, MA: Reliable Flour Company, 1911.
    Reliable Flour. Biscuit and Cakes; Success Assured. Boston, MA: Reliable Flour Company, 1915.
  - Reliable Poultry Journal Publishing Company, 1909 (Box 43, Folder 9, Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Rena-Ware Distributors, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Rena-Ware. New Ways to Cooking-Fun with Rena-Ware. Opportunity, WA: Rena-Ware Distributors, 1958.
  - Reynolds Metals Company, 1947, 1969, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Reynolds Metals Company. Reynolds Wrap; Saves Food Saves Flavor Saves Work. Richmond, VA: Reynolds Metals Company, 1947.
  - The Rheinstorm Brothers Company, 1918 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Rheinstorm Bros. Co. Rosebud Recipes for Salads, Pastries, Desserts, Fancy Dishes and Cooling Drinks. Cincinnati, OH: The Rheinstorm Bros Co., 1916.
  - Rice Council of America, 1976, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Rice Council of America. Great Dinners for Six on a Budget. Houston, TX: Rice Council of America, undated.
    Rice Council of America. Cooking for Two. Houston, TX: Rice Council of America, undated.
  - Richardson & Robbins, 1950-1955 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Richardson & Robbins. Feasts Made Fast with R & R Chicken. Dover, DE: Richardson & Robbins, undated. 1941.
  - Richmond Hotels, Inc., 1939 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Richmond Hotels Inc. Cooking of the Old Dominion Prior to 1838. Being an Interesting Collection of Directions to Guide in the Preparation of Virginia Cooking. Containing Receipts of More than One Hundred Years Ago; to Which Is Added; the Observations of the Publishers Whose Name Follows Herewith: Richmond Hotels, Inc. Presented with the Compliments of Hotel John Marshall, Hotel Richmond & Hotel Wm. Byrd Famous Hostelries of Richmond in Virginia. Richmond, VA: Whittet & Shepperson, 1939.
  - The Richmond Stove Company, 1893 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Richmond Stove Co. The Richmond Receipts with Hints and Helps for Mother, Daughter and Wife. Norwich, CT: Richmond Stove Co., 1893.
  - Rickard, Helen, 1918 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - "Ripe", circa 1900 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Label with African-American boy eating watermelon.
  - Riverbank Canning Company; Rival Manufacturing Company, circa 1910-1920s, circa 1950s (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Rival Manufacturing, Co. The Smart Hostess. Kansas City, MO: Rival Manufacturing, Co., undated.
    Riverbank Canning Co. Madonna Tomato Paste. Riverbank, CA: Riverbank Canning Company, undated.
  - Robert Timothy French Company, 1920s (Box 33, Folder 14)
    R. T. French Company. Savory Secrets; 10 Little Stories of Domestic Life; He Came Home Early and Found Her Out. No. 9. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, 1928.
    R. T. French Company. Savory Secrets; 10 Little Stories of Domestic Life; "Stay" She Implored Him. No. 6. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, 1928.
    R. T. French Company. French's Ketchup Spice; French's Chileo. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. 12th edition. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. Jr. Edition No. 13-7. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. Jr. Edition No. 13-8. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. Jr. Edition No. 13-9. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. Jr. Edition No. 13-10. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. Jr. Edition No. 14-4. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. Jr. Edition No. 14-7. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. Jr. Edition No. 14-10. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. Jr. Edition No. 15-6. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. French's Cream Salad Brand Mustard. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Salads French's Prepared Mustard. Rochester, NY: The R. T. French Company, undated.
    R. T. French Company. Made Dishes Salads and Savories with French's Cream Salad Mustard. Rochester, NY: R. T. French Co., 1925.
  - Robinson & Hale, circa 1850s (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Rochester Stamping Company, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Rochester Stamping Company. "Royal-Rochester" Casserole, Ramekin and Bean Pot Recipes. Rochester, NY: Rochester Stamping Company, 1913.
  - Rock Island Stove Company, 1887 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Rock Island Stove Co. Riverside Cook Book. Fourth edition. Rock Island, IL: Rock Island Stove Co., 1887.
  - Rockwood Brothers, circa 1900 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    Rockwood Bros. Catalogue. Chicago, IL: Rockwood Bros., circa 1900.
  - Rockwood & Company, circa 1940s (Box 33, Folder 19)
    Rockwood & Co. Rockwood Recipes. Brooklyn, NY: Consumer Relations Department, Rockwood & Co., undated.
  - Rodale Press, Inc., 1982, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Romanoff Caviar Company; Roman Meal Company, 1953, circa 1970s (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Roman Meal Co. The World's Greatest Sandwiches and a Roman Heritage of 2,000 Years. Tacoma, WA: Roman Meal Co., undated.
  - Romero, Philomena; Roquefort Association, Inc., 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Royal Baking Powder Company, 1898-1929 (Box 34, Folder 2-8)
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Rudmani, Prof. G. Royal Baker and Pastry Cook. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Company, 1898.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. The Chefs of the Cooking School. Royal Baker and Pastry Cook. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Company, 1902.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Royal Baker and Pastry Cook A Manual of Practical Receipts for Home Baking and Cooking. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Company, 1911.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Royal Baker and Pastry Cook. New York, NY: Royal Baking Company, 1911.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Recipes Showing How Cleveland's Superior Baking Powder Saves Eggs. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Co., 1917.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. New Royal Cook Book. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Co., 1920.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Le Bon Patisserie de Menage (Successful Home Baking). New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Co., 1915.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. The New Dr. Price Cook Book for Use with Dr. Price's Phosphate Baking Powder. Chicago, IL: Royal Baking Powder Co., 1921.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Table and Kitchen. New York, Chicago, Montreal: Royal Baking Powder Co., 1924.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. The Little Gingerbread Man. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Co., 1923.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Royal Cook Book. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Co., 1925.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Royal Fruit Gelatin Suggestions. New York: Royal Baking Powder, 1926.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Royal Cook Book. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Co., 1928.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Royal Cook Book. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Co., 1929.
    Royal Baking Powder Co. Le Pâtissier Royal. New York, NY: Royal Baking Powder Co., undated.
  - Royal Baking Powder Company, 1911 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Royal Baker and Pastry Cook: A Manual of Practical Receipts for Home Baking and Cooking
  - Rumford Chemical Works, circa 1876-1920s, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 9-14)
    Rumford Chemical Works. The Horsford Cook Book. Providence: Rumford Chemical Works, circa 1876.
    Rumford. The Horsford Cook Book. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, undated.
    Rumford. The Horsford Almanac and Cook Book 1881. Providence, RI: The Rumford Chemical Works, circa 1880.
    Rumford. The Horsford Almanac and Cook Book 1882. Providence, RI: The Rumford Chemical Works, circa 1881.
    Rumford. 100 Selected Recipes for Cakes, Biscuits, etc. Prepared by Ladies of Virginia. Providence, RI: Rumford Chemical Works, undated.